Guide to the Graphics collection, 1740-1995 MS2379
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Graphics, 1740-1995; Series 1
  - Twelfth Street YMCA, 12th Street N.W. between T and S Street, October 4, 1949., Circa [1993]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Young Men's Christian associations Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00799558; Young Men's Christian associations. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01183052; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Allen A.M.E. Church, 25th St. and Alabama Avenue, S.E., July 31, 1949., Circa [1993]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 739
    Cataloging notes: Title from notation on verso of photographic printing.; Reproduction by Image. 1949. 1 photographic printing In John pages Wymer Collection in the Historical Society of Washington, D.C.; Allen African Methodist Episcopal Church, Washington, D.C.; several cars and churchgoers in foreground.
    Allen African Methodist Episcopal Church (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Church buildings Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Lincoln Temple Congregational Church, 11th and R Streets, N.W., Sept. 4, 1949., Circa [1993]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 740
    Cataloging notes: Title from notation on verso of photographic printing.; Reproduction by Image. 1949. 1 photographic printing In John P. Wymer Collection in the Historical Society of Washington, D.C.; Lincoln Temple Congregational Church, Washington, D.C. front view; cars on street.
    Lincoln Temple Congregational Church, (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Church buildings Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Magruder School, M Street N.W. between 16th and 17th Streets, March 27, 1952., Circa [1993]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 27, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 742
    Cataloging notes: Title from notation on verso of photographic printing.; Reproduction by Image. 1952. 1 photographic printing In John P. Wymer Collection in the Historical Society of Washington, D.C.; Magruder School, Washington, D.C. side view.
    Magruder Elementary School (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Schools Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Central High School, 13th and Clifton Streets, N.W., June 12, 1949., Circa [1993]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 27, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 743
    Cataloging notes: Title from notation on verso of photographic printing.; Central High School, Washington, D.C.; front view.; Reproduction by Image. 1949. 1 photographic printing In John P. Wymer Collection in the Historical Society of Washington, D.C.
    Central High School (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Central High School (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00779374; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Schools Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00799558; Schools. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01107958; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Wormley Elementary School, Prospect and Bank Streets N.W., May 27, 1951., Circa [1993]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 27, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 744
    Cataloging notes: Title from notation on verso of photographic printing.; Reproduction by Image. 1951. 1 photographic printing In John P. Wymer Collection in the Historical Society of Washington, D.C.; Wormley Elementary School, Washington, D.C.; side view.
    Wormley Elementary School (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Schools Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Shaw Junior High School, 7th Street and Rhode Island Avenue, N.W., Nov. 15, 1950., Circa [1993]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 27, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 745
    Cataloging notes: Title from notation on verso of photographic printing.; Reproduction by Image. 1950. 1 photographic printing In John P. Wymer Collection in the Historical Society of Washington, D.C.; Shaw Junior High School, Washington, D.C.; street car and cars in foreground.
    Shaw Junior High School (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Schools Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Howard Theatre, Seventh Street N.W., T Street N.W. numbers 620, circa 1930., Circa [1993]; Series 1; 1 photographic print: black and white; 21 x 26 cm. (Box 27, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 747
    Cataloging notes: Title from notation on verso of photographic printing.; Howard Theatre, Washington, D.C.; important theatre for Afro-American performers.; Reproduction by Image. [circa 1930]. 1 photographic printing In Collection in the Historical Society of Washington, D.C.
    Howard Theatre (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Howard Theatre (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00761758; African Americans Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Theaters Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; African Americans. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00799558; Theaters. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01149370; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Connecticut Avenue, Washington, D.C.., Circa [1908?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 748
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Connecticut Avenue, Washington, D.C. With pedestrians, bicycle, bus.
    Connecticut Avenue (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) Connecticut Avenue. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01321945; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The Mayflower, Washington, D.C.., Circa [192-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 749
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C. at Connecticut Avenue and L Streets, crowds of people and some cars in foreground; night.
    Mayflower Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Mayflower Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00622572; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00961767; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The Mayflower, Washington, D.C.., Circa 195-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 14 x 9 cm. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 750
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Mayflower Hotel, Washington, D.C. at Connecticut Avenue and L Streets; illustration shows cars and people in foreground; autumn scene.
  - The Wardman Park Hotel, Connecticut Ave. and Woodley Road, Washington, D.C.., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 751
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Wardman Park Hotel in Washington, D.C.; now part of the Sheraton-Washington Hotel.
    Wardman Park Hotel (Washsington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Wardman Park Hotel, Washington, D.C.., Circa [195-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 752
    Wardman Park Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - The Ambassador Hotel, Washington, D.C.., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 14 x 9 cm. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 753
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Ambassador Hotel, 14th and K Streets, Washington, D.C. Shows exterior of hotel, swimming pool, and main dining room.
    Ambassador Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - The Ambassador: Washington's newest, completely air-conditioned, 500-room downtown hotel: rates include swimming pool and parking., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 14 x 9 cm. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 754
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Ambassador Hotel, 14th and K Streets, Washington, D.C. Shows exterior of hotel, swimming pool, and dining room.
    Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Ambassador Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Swimming pool, Ambassador Hotel, 14th and K Streets, N.W. Washington, D.C.., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 755
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Swimming pool at Ambassador Hotel, Washington, D.C.
  - Hi-Hat Cocktail Lounge, Ambassador Hotel, Washington, D.C.., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 756
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Cocktail lounge in Ambassador Hotel, at 14th and K Streets, Washington, D.C.
  - The Dodge Hotel on Capitol Hill, Washington 1., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 757
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Dodge Hotel, Capitol Hill, Washington, D.C.; shows a guest sitting room.
    Dodge Hotel (Washington. D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - The Hotel Raleigh., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 758
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Raleigh Hotel, Pennsylvania Avenue and 12th Streets, Washington, D.C.; shows lobby.
    Raleigh Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Raleigh Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01790810; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00961767; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The Hotel Raleigh., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 759
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Raleigh Hotel, Pennsylvania Avenue and 12th Streets, Washington, D.C.; shows Pall Mall Room and Cocktail Lounge.
  - The Raleigh, Washington, D.C.., Circa [192-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 14 x 9 cm. (Box 28, Folder 13)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 760
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Raleigh Hotel, Pennsylvania Avenue and 12th Streets, Washington, D.C.; shows exterior of hotel with cars parked in front.
  - Hotel Hamilton, 14th and K Sts., N.W., Washington, D.C.., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 14 x 9 cm. (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 761
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Hotel Hamilton, Washington, D.C.; shows exterior with cars parked in front.
    Hotel Hamilton (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Pennsylvania Avenue, Washington, D.C.., Circa [191-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 762
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; View of Pennsylvania Avenue from White House.
  - Pennsylvania Avenue, Washington, D.C.., Circa [192-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 763
    Cataloging notes: Copies have slight variations in coloration.; Post card.; Pennsylvania Avenue, Washington, D.C., seen from the steps of the U.S. Treasury Building.
  - Thomas Circle, Washington, D.C.., Circa [ 1930]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 764
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Post card.; Thomas Circle, Washington, D.C.
  - Thomas Circle showing underpass., Circa [1948?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 18)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 765
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Thomas Circle, Washington, D.C.; shows underpass and National City Christian Church in the background.
  - Thomas Circle and Lutheran Church, Washington, D.C.., Circa [191-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 19)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 766
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Thomas Circle, Washington, D.C.
  - Thomas Circle, looking North, Washington, D.C.., Circa [192-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 20)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 767
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.
  - Thomas Circle, Washington, D.C.., Circa [ 1900]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 21)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 768
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Post card.; Thomas Circle, Washington, D.C.; streetcar, pedestrians, and horse and buggies.
  - Thomas Circle, Washington, D.C.., Circa [191-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 22)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 769
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Thomas Circle, Washington, D.C.; streetcar and pedestrians.
  - Looking up Pennsylvania Ave. from 9th St., Washington, D.C.., Circa [1909?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 23)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 770
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Post card.; Pennsylvania Avenue, Washington, D.C.; U.S. Capitol building visible; streetcars, pedestrians, cars.
  - The Shoreham Hotel: resort hotel in the nation's capital., Circa 194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 24)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 771
    Cataloging notes: No Washingtoniana Vertical File number.; Post card.; Shoreham Hotel at Connecticut Ave. at Calvert Street, N.W., Washington, D.C.
    Shoreham Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Shoreham Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01792539; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00961767; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Shoreham Hotel, Washington, D.C.., Circa [1908?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 25)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 772
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Shoreham Hotel, 15th and H Street, N.W. Washington, D.C.; now at 2500 Calvert St., N.W.
  - G Street, Washington, D.C.., Circa [190-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 26)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 773
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; G Street, N.W. Washington, D.C.; streetcars, pedestrians, horse and buggies.
  - Dodge Hotel, Washington, D.C.., Circa [193-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 27)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 774
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Dodge Hotel, Capitol Hill, Washington, D.C.; cars are shown in foreground.
    Dodge Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - F Street, N.W., Washington, D.C.., Circa [1912?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 28)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 775
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; F Street at 9th Street, N.W., Washington, D.C.; U.S. Treasury Building visible; streetcars and pedestrians.
  - Aerial photograph of Washington: Wardman Park Hotel in foreground., Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 29)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 776
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Washington, D.C.: Wardman Park Hotel in foreground with Rock Creek Park and Washington Monument in background.
  - The new Willard Hotel, the finest in Washington, D.C.., Circa [190-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 14 x 9 cm. (Box 28, Folder 30)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 777
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Willard Hotel, Washington, D.C.; Pennsylvania Avenue, and 14th Street, N.W.; pedestrians and horse and buggies.
    Willard Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Willard Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00663413; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00961767; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - New Willard Hotel, Washington, D.C.., Circa 190-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 31)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 778
  - Thomas Circle looking south showing Cumberland and Portland Apartments, Washington, D.C.., Circa [1912]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 32)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 779
    Cataloging notes: Postcard.; Thomas Circle, Washington, D.C.; pedestrians and horse and buggies.
  - Dupont Park, Washington, D.C.., Circa [1911?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 33)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 780
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Dupont Circle, Washington, D.C.; shows statue of Samuel F. Du Pont, pedestrians in the park.
    Du Pont, Samuel Francis, 1803-1865 Monuments Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Du Pont, Samuel Francis, 1803-1865. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00173364; Monuments. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01025892; Dupont Circle (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Washington (D.C.) Dupont Circle. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01316866; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Statue of Rear Adml Samuel F. Dupont, by Launt Thompson, Washington, D.C.., Circa [191-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 34)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 781
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Dupont Circle, Washington D.C.; shows statue of Samuel F. Du Pont.
  - The Dodge Hotel on Capitol Hill., Circa [193-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 35)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 782
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Dodge Hotel, Capitol Hill, Washington, D.C.; exterior view with cars on street.
  - The Dodge Hotel on Capitol Hill., Circa [193-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 36)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 783
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Dodge Hotel, Capitol Hill, Washington, D.C.; interior view of the lounge.
  - The National Hotel, Washington, D.C.., Circa 190-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 37)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 784
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; National Hotel, 6th and Pennsylvania Ave., Washington, D.C.; exterior with pedestrians.
    National Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; National Hotel (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00728855; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00961767; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - The new Varnum Hotel., Circa 192-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 15 cm. (Box 28, Folder 38)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 785
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Varnum Hotel, New Jersey Avenue and C Streets, S.E., Washington, D.C.; U.S. Capitol building visible.
    Varnum Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - The new Oxford Hotel, 15th and Pa. Ave., N.W. Washington, D.C.., Circa [1924?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 39)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 786
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Oxford Hotel, 15th and Pennsylvania Avenue, N.W., Washington, D.C., exterior view.
    Oxford Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - Boulder Bridge, Rock Creek Park, Washington, D.C.., Circa [1911?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 40)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 787
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; The Boulder Bridge in Rock Creek Park, Washington, D.C.; side view.
    Rock Creek Park (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Washington (D.C.) Rock Creek Park. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01316422; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01423874
  - Scene in Rock Creek, Washington, D.C.., Circa [191-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 28, Folder 41)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 788
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; A bridge in Rock Creek Park, Washington, D.C.
  - Boulder Bridge, Rock Creek Park, Washington, D.C.., Circa [191-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 789
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Boulder Bridge in Rock Creek Park, Washington, D.C.
  - Georgetown University dormitories, showing statue of John Carroll: Copley Hall and White Gravenor Building, Washington, D.C., Circa [1946?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 790
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Georgetown University, Washington, D.C.
  - The Woodward and Lothrop Store, F and G, 10th and 11th Streets: Washington's shopping center., Circa [1916?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - The new Colonial Hotel, Circa [194-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 792
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Colonial Hotel, Washington, D.C.; side view with cars in front.
    Colonial Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.
  - The new Colonial Hotel., Circa 1936?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 14 x 9 cm. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 793
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Colonial Hotel, 15th and M Streets, N.W., Washington, D.C.; front view with cars in front.
  - Main dining room, National Hotel, Washington, D.C.., Circa [191-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 794
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Dining room at the National Hotel, Pennsylvania Avenue at 6th Street, between the Capitol and the White House, Washington, D.C.
  - National Hotel winter garden, Washington, D.C.., Circa [191-?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction: color; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 795
  - Grafton Hotel, Connecticut Avenue and De Sales Street, Washington, D.C.., Circa [1936?]; Series 1; 1 photomechanical reproduction; 9 x 14 cm. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Original catalog no. GRAPHIC 796
    Cataloging notes: Post card.; Grafton Hotel, 1139 Connecticut Avenue, N.W., Washington, D.C.; front view with cars in front.
    Grafton Hotel (Washington, D.C.) Pictorial works.; Hotels Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.